<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Girls with Deep Pockets</title>
    <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Girls with Deep Pockets</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Stephanie Locke. Site made using [Hugo](//gohugo.io) and the [Icarus](https://github.com/digitalcraftsman/hugo-icarus-theme) theme.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 11:23:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Poche Posh</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/poche-posh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 11:23:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/poche-posh/</guid>
      <description>@gwdeeppockets have you seen @pocheposh? would love to see more stores with international shipping beyond North America!
&amp;mdash; &amp;amp;#39;kæ-rɪl\ (@pohutukaryl) May 30, 2017 
From our Twitter feed, we had a great suggestion - Poche Posh as they not only put pockets right up front in the core mission statement but they ship internationally!
Poche Posh are beautifully in your face about pockets. They felt the pain and are doing something about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles worth reading (1st Nov 2016)</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/articles-worth-reading-1st-nov-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 10:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/articles-worth-reading-1st-nov-2016/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been fantastic to see that there&amp;rsquo;s actually a huge proportion of women out there demanding pockets. As a result, there&amp;rsquo;s been some nifty articles on the web that are well worth reading.
 Our Fave Places: Line Cut Supply Article interviewing a Sheffield, UK based designer of womens workwear. Aimee insists on pocket in all her designs! Hello Giggles: 11 stages of fake pockets being the worst fashion LIE of all time Gif&amp;rsquo;s ahoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pockets are for safety</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/pockets-are-for-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 10:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/pockets-are-for-safety/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s wrong with the woman in the picture? She has no pockets!
Her (choice of) clothing means she&amp;rsquo;s having to keep her phone, ID, keys, money, and other vital items in a single, easy to steal item. Being unable to distribute important items around her body leaves her extremely vulnerable in the event of a crime.
A lot of safety / pickpocket prevention tips involve the use of pockets, especially zippable or internal pockets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building cool stuff</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/building-cool-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 10:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/building-cool-stuff/</guid>
      <description>I (Steph), the main author, am a techy and in particular I&amp;rsquo;m a data focussed techy who loves building open source things. One of the nifty things I think that could be done with this site is use it to build some cool open source tools for bringing the message of pockets to the masses!
We can do things like:
 commiserating with people who are lacking pockets (not funds, but actual pockets) celebrating with people who do have pockets promoting companies who are showcasing products that have lots of pockets and are aimed at women gathering pocket related news from the internet  As well nifty analytical challenges, there are also other technical and non-technical ways to get involved with the site, from extending the site to writing posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Pockets</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/tweetstreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 16:56:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/tweetstreams/</guid>
      <description>Got Pockets - Curated tweets by gwdeeppockets 
Where&amp;#39;s my Pockets - Curated tweets by gwdeeppockets</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCOTTeVEST</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/scottevest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 10:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/scottevest/</guid>
      <description>@gwdeeppockets well, there&amp;#39;s always @scottevest
&amp;mdash; Aaron Nelson (@SQLvariant) October 27, 2016 
From our Twitter feed yesterday we had a great suggestion - SCOTTeVEST.
SCOTTeVEST literally sprang out of a desire for more (and smarter) pockets. Fed up with having to offload a purse on to her husband and fed up with having to carry her purse, Laura and Scott started SCOTTeVEST.
We love the solidarity and mission for this company!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gudrun Sjödén</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/gudrun-sj%C3%B6d%C3%A9n/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/gudrun-sj%C3%B6d%C3%A9n/</guid>
      <description>Found in the comments section of the article Women&amp;rsquo;s clothes are still utterly impractical - where are my pockets? is a recommendation from one Anne Wareham.
Ann had this to say:
 [Gudren] deserves credit for making comfortable, interesting clothing for women. With pockets. Xxx
 Gudrun is a female designer with an ethical bent who has been in fashion for 40 years now. Even some of her earliest sketches have fantasticly big pockets!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eShakti</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/eshakti/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/eshakti/</guid>
      <description>Wow, our first submission from the audience and it&amp;rsquo;s great. R posted about this nifty looking online retailer called eShakti.
R had this to say:
 These pockets are huge! Not every single item on the site has pockets, but most of the dresses and skirts have very large pockets. Pockets are large enough to fit an iPhone and a small wallet or other items and on fuller skirted designs, you can&amp;rsquo;t ever tell there&amp;rsquo;s anything in your pockets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About GwDP</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/about-gwdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/about-gwdp/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Girls with Deep Pockets!
I&amp;rsquo;m Steph and I&amp;rsquo;ve been continuously disappointed by the lack of pockets in my clothes for years. They&amp;rsquo;re either missing, fake, or hopelessly inadequate for fitting anything reasonable like a phone in them.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know whether it&amp;rsquo;s the fashion industry&amp;rsquo;s focus on trying to make us look awesome, and sacrificing convenience on the way, or whether it&amp;rsquo;s actually a conspiracy to force us into the purchase of handbags, and adding dramatically to their bottom line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show off some pockets</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 16:56:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Let us know about a great item of clothing, a fab designer or store, or feel free to talk to us about pockets! You can also you can submit your own post if you&amp;rsquo;re feeling technical.
Hey Steph,
My name is and
my email address is  I wanted to let you know about   You can find out more at this You may also find this picture handy   send    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submitting a post</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/submitting-a-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 16:56:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/submitting-a-post/</guid>
      <description>To submit a post directly to the site, then at the moment it requires you to be reasonably comfortable with GitHub and markdown.
 If that&amp;rsquo;s put you off, simply fill in this form which asks you for information and we&amp;rsquo;ll get around to penning a blog post on your behalf.
 Getting ready to write your post  Fork this repository (stephlocke/girlswithdeeppockets) to your own GitHub account Clone this to your computer Create a new file called [SOMETHINGRELEVANT].</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>