<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clothes With Pockets on Girls with Deep Pockets</title>
    <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/tags/clothes-with-pockets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Clothes With Pockets on Girls with Deep Pockets</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Stephanie Locke. Site made using [Hugo](//gohugo.io) and the [Icarus](https://github.com/digitalcraftsman/hugo-icarus-theme) theme.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 11:23:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/tags/clothes-with-pockets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Poche Posh</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/poche-posh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 11:23:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/poche-posh/</guid>
      <description>@gwdeeppockets have you seen @pocheposh? would love to see more stores with international shipping beyond North America!
&amp;mdash; &amp;amp;#39;kæ-rɪl\ (@pohutukaryl) May 30, 2017 
From our Twitter feed, we had a great suggestion - Poche Posh as they not only put pockets right up front in the core mission statement but they ship internationally!
Poche Posh are beautifully in your face about pockets. They felt the pain and are doing something about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCOTTeVEST</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/scottevest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 10:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/scottevest/</guid>
      <description>@gwdeeppockets well, there&amp;#39;s always @scottevest
&amp;mdash; Aaron Nelson (@SQLvariant) October 27, 2016 
From our Twitter feed yesterday we had a great suggestion - SCOTTeVEST.
SCOTTeVEST literally sprang out of a desire for more (and smarter) pockets. Fed up with having to offload a purse on to her husband and fed up with having to carry her purse, Laura and Scott started SCOTTeVEST.
We love the solidarity and mission for this company!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gudrun Sjödén</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/gudrun-sj%C3%B6d%C3%A9n/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/gudrun-sj%C3%B6d%C3%A9n/</guid>
      <description>Found in the comments section of the article Women&amp;rsquo;s clothes are still utterly impractical - where are my pockets? is a recommendation from one Anne Wareham.
Ann had this to say:
 [Gudren] deserves credit for making comfortable, interesting clothing for women. With pockets. Xxx
 Gudrun is a female designer with an ethical bent who has been in fashion for 40 years now. Even some of her earliest sketches have fantasticly big pockets!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eShakti</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/eshakti/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/eshakti/</guid>
      <description>Wow, our first submission from the audience and it&amp;rsquo;s great. R posted about this nifty looking online retailer called eShakti.
R had this to say:
 These pockets are huge! Not every single item on the site has pockets, but most of the dresses and skirts have very large pockets. Pockets are large enough to fit an iPhone and a small wallet or other items and on fuller skirted designs, you can&amp;rsquo;t ever tell there&amp;rsquo;s anything in your pockets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>