<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gwdp on Girls with Deep Pockets</title>
    <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/categories/gwdp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gwdp on Girls with Deep Pockets</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Stephanie Locke. Site made using [Hugo](//gohugo.io) and the [Icarus](https://github.com/digitalcraftsman/hugo-icarus-theme) theme.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 10:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/categories/gwdp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building cool stuff</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/building-cool-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 10:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/building-cool-stuff/</guid>
      <description>I (Steph), the main author, am a techy and in particular I&amp;rsquo;m a data focussed techy who loves building open source things. One of the nifty things I think that could be done with this site is use it to build some cool open source tools for bringing the message of pockets to the masses!
We can do things like:
 commiserating with people who are lacking pockets (not funds, but actual pockets) celebrating with people who do have pockets promoting companies who are showcasing products that have lots of pockets and are aimed at women gathering pocket related news from the internet  As well nifty analytical challenges, there are also other technical and non-technical ways to get involved with the site, from extending the site to writing posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About GwDP</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/about-gwdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/about-gwdp/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Girls with Deep Pockets!
I&amp;rsquo;m Steph and I&amp;rsquo;ve been continuously disappointed by the lack of pockets in my clothes for years. They&amp;rsquo;re either missing, fake, or hopelessly inadequate for fitting anything reasonable like a phone in them.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know whether it&amp;rsquo;s the fashion industry&amp;rsquo;s focus on trying to make us look awesome, and sacrificing convenience on the way, or whether it&amp;rsquo;s actually a conspiracy to force us into the purchase of handbags, and adding dramatically to their bottom line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show off some pockets</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 16:56:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Let us know about a great item of clothing, a fab designer or store, or feel free to talk to us about pockets! You can also you can submit your own post if you&amp;rsquo;re feeling technical.
Hey Steph,
My name is and
my email address is  I wanted to let you know about   You can find out more at this You may also find this picture handy   send    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submitting a post</title>
      <link>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/submitting-a-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 16:56:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://girlswithdeeppockets.com/submitting-a-post/</guid>
      <description>To submit a post directly to the site, then at the moment it requires you to be reasonably comfortable with GitHub and markdown.
 If that&amp;rsquo;s put you off, simply fill in this form which asks you for information and we&amp;rsquo;ll get around to penning a blog post on your behalf.
 Getting ready to write your post  Fork this repository (stephlocke/girlswithdeeppockets) to your own GitHub account Clone this to your computer Create a new file called [SOMETHINGRELEVANT].</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>